Director.
Director,
you're really amazing.
I've become a fan of yours.
You don't have to say that.
After all, this is my profession.
Director,
did I do a really bad job these past two days?
I can only say
it was expected.
Director.
Actually...
I...
Let me go over the upcoming rehearsal schedule with you first.
Let's go and go over it.
Director,
I still have many things
I want to discuss with you.
How about we
talk another day.
Today's rehearsal is over.
Director,
you don't understand what I mean.
I mean we should
pick another day to talk.
I know what you mean.
You're the one who doesn't understand me.
I mean,
today's rehearsal is over.
We'll have another rehearsal tomorrow.
Why don't we
talk tomorrow?
No, director,
you really don't get what I mean.
I mean tonight is
the day we pick.
What do you mean pick a day?
Pick what day?
Alright, let's talk some other day.
Jinxi.
Goodbye.
Director.
What do you want to talk to me about?
Open it.
What would you like to drink?
I'm sorry.
Did I interrupt your business?
It's not what you think.
What are you doing?
Director.
I've decided that starting today,
I will officially hire you as my musical theater acting coach.
You can name your price.
What are you thinking?
Besides the weekends,
we have to rehearse every day.
I don't have time to give you private lessons.
But I need to improve.
To be honest, these past few days,
I feel like there's a huge gap between me and everyone else.
Also,
that exercise you mentioned,
I really don't know what to say to everyone.
Director.
Did choosing me
cause you
a lot of trouble?
I know
you really want to fit in.
But it's still hard for you right now.
Why?
Which actor do you see coming to class
with their manager and assistant accompanying them the whole time?
What I need is an actor,
not a star.
If in our daily communication we have to consider
whether what we said
needs a non-disclosure agreement,
how can we cooperate?
Director.
I won't let Sister Hu and Eason come next time.
It's not just that.
Jin Xi,
I can't see the real you.
The real me?
I've seen your music videos.
Your outfits,
your smiles,
your specific postures,
none of them are not carefully designed.
You,
seem very enthusiastic on the surface,
but actually keep your distance from everyone.
It makes it impossible to reach the real you.
No, director.
I am who I am.
I have nothing to hide.
Do you know why we usually
do those exercises?
Why?
These basic exercises have a collective name,
called liberating one's nature.
Liberating one's nature?
My nature is quite liberated.
I am super liberated.
No.
On the contrary, you are not liberated at all.
You have a very thick protective shell.
So, Jin Xi,
what you need to do now
is to put away
your overly prominent personality
and return to a state of nothingness.
Forget the flamboyant Jin Xi,
return to the simplest state,
and tell me
who you really are.
To well portray the Ning Caichen in my mind,
you must let me see
the most real
and sincere Jin Xi.
Okay?
Director.
Can you stop popping out of nowhere?
Sorry.
I'd like to do another
life storytelling.
My mom gave me this guitar when I was a kid.
She's the one who taught me how to play.
My mom also taught me a really cool way to play,
which is playing while lying down.
Why?
Because she said that
playing standing up for too long hurts your back,
playing sitting down hurts your shoulders,
and only playing lying down is the most comfortable
and effortless.
When I was with my mom,
no matter how naughty I was,
she would never stop me.
But my dad would get very angry when he saw it,
and he would scold me every time.
As soon as I saw my dad was about to scold me,
I would immediately run to my mom.
And then I would learn to play the guitar with her.
This way, when my dad saw
that I was learning the guitar,
he wouldn't scold me anymore.
Then my mom would teach me how to hum a song.
We would hum for a long, long time,
and her voice would get softer and softer.
Then my mom would give me money to buy candy.
I would go out to play for a while
before coming back.
When I came back, I found that
my mom was full of energy again.
When I was a kid, I always wondered
why
my mom didn't live in the same house as us.
Later, I found out
that my mom
was seriously ill.
Even then,
she would, every day,
teach me to play the guitar,
because
she wanted to pass on
the thing she loved most
to me, the one she loved most.
Later,
I took the first chord she taught me
and turned it into a complete single.
That was also my debut single.
Are my requirements for him
too strict?
Feixin, you're in great shape.
Please take your seat.
How was it?
Great.
I hope everyone can be in great shape like Feixin.
Jinxi,
come on stage.
Okay.
Your profile says you excel at dancing.
Can you show us a little?
Okay.
Jinxi's dance video
on social media
got 3.658 million likes.
The numbers are still going up.
Jinxi,
this is our dance choreographer, Mr. Qingsong.
Mr. Qingsong,
do you have anything to say?
You dance hip-hop.
Our show
features classical dance.
You are used to lowering your body
and dropping your center of gravity.
This goes against the upright posture required in classical dance.
It's like
an animal used to rolling in the mud
can never become a singing swan.
Mr. Qingsong, how about this.
You can test Jinxi's dance basics.
Follow me.
One, two, three, four.
I got it.
Can you keep up?
Not bad.
Two, two, three. Can you keep up?
Yes, I can.
Open.
Down.
Three, four.
Five, six, down, seven, eight.
Two, two, up, turn.
Good.
You try it once.
Director.
I believe everyone
already knows Jin Xi's dance skills.
Are you laughing? Is it funny?
Tell you what.
Let's start with the most basic
trust exercises.
Relax.
You must fully trust your partner.
Right.
Understood.
Thank you, Qingsong.
Please return to your seat.
Okay.
Jin Xi.
Trust exercises build chemistry between actors.
You give it a try.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just a little nervous.
Good thing we have chemistry.
Good thing we have great chemistry.
Bye.
You two need to practice that move again.
Okay.
Bye.
Pay attention to it.
Let me see.
Don't change my words.
Because we designed it so that
you two would interact.
So you...
Xiaoqi.
Jin Xi, stop practicing.
You have made a lot of progress.
Really?
Tomorrow is a day off.
We can hang out together.
Getting familiar with each other
is better for our creation.
Team building?
Sure.
No.
I mean...
Let's all go together.
Team building tomorrow.
Sure.
Sorry.
I have a family gathering tomorrow.
Definitely next time.
It's fine.
You're not going, Mr. Du?
Baibai.
Then are you going, Baibai?
It's up to you.
Didn't you say I should ask for your opinion on everything?
My opinion right now is to listen to you.
Then Jiaoye and Big Cousin are definitely going.
Are you going, Director?
I'm going.
That's rare, Director.
Jinxi, don't arrange any outdoor activities.
Our Wanwan has delicate skin and can't take it.
I'm not that delicate.
You're so annoying.
Okay.
I'll send the address to the group chat later.
Don't be late.
Group chat? What group chat? Add me.
Right, we don't have each other's WeChat yet.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
I'll add you to the group chat later.
Okay.
I can just add you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
All right.
Added you.
We should get going.
All right, bye.
Bye.
See you tomorrow.
What are you fooling around for?
What do you mean, fooling around?
Do you think I can't tell?
Are you trying to get close to Jinxi to use her for clout?
I just want to act like a couple to get some clout.
You have no idea.
It'll be awesome if it goes viral.
Fine, but know your limits.
Make sure it doesn't affect the rehearsal.
Baby,
do you remember the last time
we played here?
Look, it's still this one.
I was scared to death by that female ghost.
Good thing I had you to protect me.
Why are you dressed like a special forces soldier for an escape room?
Bring more things.
Better safe than sorry.
Why isn't Feixin here yet?
Sorry.
I'm late.
Jinxi, you look so handsome today.
You guys came too.
Of course we came.
I didn't know you guys were coming.
I only bought five tickets.
What should we do?
Only five of us can go in.
It's fine.
I guess Eason and Sister Hu wouldn't like it anyway.
We can just go in.
How's the privacy here?
Don't worry, it's very private.
A friend of mine runs it.
I've already talked to them.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
This place is really fun.
Every NPC inside is professional.
I can't wait.
Baby, you have to protect me.
I'm scared.
David.
If you see any physical contact
like holding hands or leaning against Jinxi's chest later,
you must remember to take pictures for me.
Sure, you are a good customer, so no problem.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
Come in.
Don't scare me.
AD
3025.
Earth was invaded by zombies.
It's the end of the world
and people are suffering.
I was infected,
and although I used antivenom,
there are still
sequelae.
And you
are the last few people who have never been infected with the virus.
You are the last hope of humanity.
Attention, everyone.
My patience is shorter than a zombie's fingernails.
Now your task is
to find the serum bank with the sun logo.
This is your final task.
I wish you
safety.
Stay safe.
All right, the game officially begins now.
Let's team up in pairs.
But there are only five of us now. What should we do?
Baby,
I'll definitely team up with you.
It's fine. I happen to like acting alone.
Jinxi, that's great!
We'll be a team.
Excuse me.
Are you interested in making some extra money?
Jinxi, are you scared?
A little.
A little? I'm quite scared.
The NPC just said
we need to find props in here.
But I'm a bit scared.
Let's do this together.
Hold my hand.
Jinxi.
Jinxi,
where are you going?
Where are you chasing me to?
Sister Hu.
No way.
How could you still recognize me like this?
How could I not recognize you?
I'm telling you.
Stay away from that Bai... whatever her name is.
Stay far away from her.
She's definitely up to no good.
I think she's fine.
Trust me on this.
My eyes are like a ruler.
I'm never wrong about people.
Go on and have fun.
I'll go keep an eye on her.
Go.
Watch me.
Do you really think you can scare me like this?
In the whole room,
this is the only place to hide.
Of course I'd know you're here.
Come on, do your performance again.
Have you seen zombies in those doomsday movies?
A zombie's muscles should be stiff,
but your limbs are too loose.
What you need to do now
is to engage all your muscles.
Like me. Come on, do it.
Feel your muscles engaging,
getting stiff.
You are a zombie now.
Do it.
That's better. Do it again.
Not hard enough. Keep going.
And your vocal placement
shouldn't be in your throat.
Inhale.
No. Relax your chest.
Inhale all the way down,
down to where I just touched.
Feel my fingers.
Vocalize.
Harder.
Feel my fingers.
Use your chest.
Harder. Keep going. Come on.
Jin Xi, I finally found you.
I'm so scared. A ghost keeps chasing me.
To be honest,
I also have a dream of becoming an actor.
It's been years since I graduated,
and I still haven't found a good job.
Actually, studying acting
makes it really hard to find a job.
As for joining a crew,
there are so many of them that I don't know which one to go to.
If I sign with an agency,
I'm afraid of getting scammed.
You see, I've studied dance and acting since I was a kid.
I don't know what career to switch to now.
I understand.
I'm exhausted.
Jinxi, I finally found you.
We meet again.
Why is it you again?
Start running, baby.
I really don't know what you're mad about.
We agreed to adventure and run together.
Why did you run ahead?
I'm a girl.
Are you expecting me to protect you?
Get back.
We're in the middle of an argument.
Can't you read the room?
Of course I can protect you.
But only if we stay together.
I don't want to listen, I don't, I don't!
If you don't listen, I'll be mad, mad, mad!
Jin Xi.
Aren't you in a group with Bai Feixin?
Due to some human factors,
we got separated.
I found the virus serum.
There should be a way out.
Doctor.
I'm just an old woman
struggling to survive in this chaotic world.
This incredibly handsome young man,
do you have the virus serum?
Give it to me.
I can show you a way out.
Can you really take us out?
She's just an old lady.
Give it to her.
This road,
I've walked it for over seventy years.
Come, I'll show you the way.
Come in.
Find a way.
I'm sorry.
Every man for himself,
or heaven and earth will destroy him.
Just starve to death in there.
I wouldn't even laugh if you screamed.
I'm off work.
I told you we shouldn't have given it to her.
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
How are we supposed to get out of here?
Don't you think
it's just like when we were in...
Shut up.
Didn't you say you weren't afraid of these things?
I'm not afraid of ghosts,
but I really hate dark and small places like this.
It's okay.
They can't possibly
lock us up here forever.
This place seems to be a hidden door.
Go this way.